( knocking on door )
HEY.
HI. MY NAME'S
CHANDLER.
I JUST MOVED
IN NEXT DOOR
AND I WAS WONDERING IF YOU'D
BE INTERESTED IN BATTLING ME
IN A POST-APOCALYPTIC
WORLD FOR CONTROL
OF THE GALAXY'S LAST
REMAINING ENERGY SOURCE?
SURE, NEIGHBOR.
COME ON IN.
SO, IS JANINE AROUND?
UH, NO, SHE'S AT DANCE CLASS.
CAN I SEE
WHAT SHE DID WITH MY ROOM?
YEAH, BUT, HEY,
DON'T GO THROUGH HER STUFF.
SHE GETS REALLY MAD.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT IS THI...
IT'S LIKE A GUY NEVER LIVED
IN HERE.
LOOK, YOU GOT TO BE CAREFUL.
THIS GIRL THING IS DANGEROUS.
IT'S SPREADING ALREADY.
IT IS?
YES, IS THIS
YOUR PRETTY PINK PILLOW
ON THE COUCH?
NO.
IS THAT YOUR
TINY LITTLE BOX
THAT'S TOO SMALL
TO PUT ANYTHING IN?
NO.
NO. OKAY, THIS IS NOT GOOD.
YOU ARE A GUY, OKAY?
THIS IS A
GUY'S PLACE.
IF YOU LET THIS GO,
YOU'LL BE SITTING AROUND
WITH YOUR FINGERS
SOAKING IN STUFF.
ALL RIGHT,
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'LL-I'LL-I'LL TALK
TO HER.
YES, TALK TO HER--
BE A MAN.
I'M A MAN.
DEFEND YOURSELF.
( grunts )
CHANDLER,
COME ON.
WE HAVE TO HEM
THE NEW DUST RUFFLE.
BE RIGHT THERE,
SWEETUMS.
OKAY.
A TOTALLY DIFFERENT
SITUATION.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HEY, GUYS.
HEY, HOW WAS YOUR BREAKFAST
WITH HILLARY?
IT WAS OKAY.
SHE'S STILL KINDA DEPRESSED
BECAUSE SHE BROKE UP
WITH HER BOYFRIEND.
WELL, IS THIS HILLARY
YOUR HOT ASSISTANT CHEF HILLARY?
YEAH.
THE ONE THAT ALWAYS STARES AT ME
WHEN I COME IN?
NO, THE ONE WHO
LOOKED AT YOU ONCE
BECAUSE YOU
GOT IN HER WAY.
STILL, I COULD TELL SHE WAS
INTO ME.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU SET US UP?
OOH, ARE YOU SETTING ROSS UP
WITH SOMEONE?
DOES SHE HAVE A WEDDING DRESS?
HEY.
RACHEL?
YEAH?
LISTEN, I'M, UM,
MAKING UP FLYERS
TRYING TO GET
NEW MASSAGE CLIENTS.
SO, CAN I COME TO BLOOMINGDALE'S
AND USE THE COPY MACHINE?
WELL, SURE, BUT THEY MIGHT
THINK IT'S KIND OF WEIRD
CONSIDERING I DON'T
WORK THERE ANYMORE.
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT HAPPENED?
I-I GOT A JOB
AT RALPH LAUREN.
WELL, THAT'S GREAT!
CONGRATULATIONS!
WOW!
( chuckling ):
A YEAR AGO.
YOU'VE LASTED
A WHOLE YEAR.
GOOD FOR YOU.
OH.
( chuckles )
BUT, PHEEBS,
YOU-YOU CAN STILL USE
THE COPY MACHINE
WHERE I ACTUALLY WORK.
BUT JUST COME
BY AT LUNCH
SO THAT MY BOSS
DOESN'T SEE YOU
'CAUSE KIM WILL
JUST FREAK OUT
AND SHE ALREADY DOESN'T
LIKE ME VERY MUCH.
I DON'T THINK MY BOSS
LIKES ME, EITHER.
I DON'T THINK MINE
MAYBE IT'S A UNIVERSAL THING.
OR MAYBE... IT'S
BECAUSE YOU'RE ALL
HANGING AROUND HERE
AT 11:30
ON A WEDNESDAY.
YEAH, LET'S HEAD
OFF TO WORK.
WE SHOULD GO.
THANK YOU.
SURE.
NOW, YOU WILL NOT
BELIEVE THIS
BUT I WAS IN THE COPY ROOM,
MAKING COPIES
AND RALPH LAUREN CAME IN.
OH, MY GOD.
DID YOU TALK TO HIM?
YEAH, A LITTLE.
HE SEEMS REALLY NICE.
GOOD KISSER.
WHAT?
YOU KISSED HIM?
TOTALLY.
( gasps )
PHOEBE, ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YEAH. I WAS JUST IN THERE.
HE CAME IN,
HE INTRODUCED HIMSELF
AND, THEN, NEXT THING I KNOW,
WE'RE MAKING OUT, YOU KNOW.
PHOEBE, I MEAN,
YOU DO KNOW HE'S MARRIED?
NO.
PHOEBE...
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO--
ASK EVERY GUY I MAKE OUT WITH
IF HE'S MARRIED?
NO, YEAH, I SHOULD, I SHOULD.
HEY, JOEY.
HEY.
UH, CAN I
TALK TO YOU
FOR A SECOND?
THIS, UH, KID
IN THIS PICTURE.
DO YOU, UH, YOU KNOW THIS KID?
IS THAT LIKE A RELATIVE
OR SOMETHING?
NO, I JUST THOUGHT IT WAS CUTE.
YEAH, THAT'S
WHAT I WAS AFRAID OF.
OKAY, UH...
LOOK, JANINE,
I REALLY WANT YOU
TO FEEL AT HOME HERE
BUT SOME OF THIS NEW STUFF,
IT'S JUST... IT'S TOO GIRLIE.
OH.
LIKE WHAT?
LIKE THIS--
PICTURES OF CUTE BABIES
WE DON'T KNOW.
WE-WE CAN'T HAVE THAT.
JOEY, IT'S ANNE GEDDES.
SHE'S A FAMOUS ARTIST.
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW THIS BABY.
I DON'T KNOW
IF SHE'S A FAMOUS ARTIST OR NOT
YOU KNOW, AND...
I DON'T WANT TO BE A JERK
BUT YOU'RE-YOU'RE CHANGING
TOO MUCH AROUND HERE.
WELL, I'M SORRY,
I JUST THOUGHT I'D TRY
AND MAKE THE PLACE
A LITTLE NICER.
YEAH, BUT IT'S-IT'S
TOO MUCH STUFF.
YOU KNOW,
LIKE YOU GOT THE CANDLES
AND THE FOOFY
SCHMOOFER THING HERE
AND, THEN, OVER HERE
YOU GOT A PICTURE
OF A WATERING CAN.
WELL, I JUST THOUGHT...
I'M SURE IT'S
A FAMOUS WATERING CAN, OKAY,
BUT, COME ON...
AND WHAT IS
WITH THE REALLY HOT STICK
IN THE BATHROOM?
IT'S A CURLING IRON.
OH.
WELL-WELL, THAT'S OKAY, THEN...
BUT, OKAY, MY TOWELS
FOR INSTANCE, OKAY.
I COME INTO
THE BATHROOM HERE
AND MY TOWEL IS NOT
ON THE FLOOR WHERE I KEEP IT.
IT'S UP HERE,
ON SOME HOOK
AND...
SMELLS DIFFERENT.
IT'S CLEAN.
YEAH, WELL,
IT FEELS DIFFERENT.
IT'S DRY.
ALL RIGHT, I CAN MAKE MY PEACE
WITH THE CLEAN, DRY TOWELS...
AND, OKAY, ALSO WHAT IS
WITH THESE CHIPS YOU BOUGHT?
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S POTPOURRI.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO SMELL IT.
( voice cracking ):
WELL, THAT'S LIKE SUMMER
IN A BOWL.
OH.
KIM, HI.
UH-HUH.
( clears throat )
SO, YOU KNOW, I-I-I HANDED
IN THAT MARKETING REPORT
AND I... AND I NEVER GOT
TO HEAR WHAT YOU THOUGHT.
I DIDN'T READ IT.
AH.
( sighs )
SO, WOW, THE SPRING LINE--
IT'S REALLY GOING TO BE
GREAT THIS YEAR, HUH?
YEAH.
( sighs )
SO, I HEAR, UH, RALPH
LAUREN FOOLED AROUND
WITH SOMEONE IN
THE COPY ROOM.
TELL ME EVERYTHING.
HEY, GUYS.
HEY.
WHAT'S UP?
YOU KNOW...
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR TEETH?
I WHITENED THEM.
REALLY?
YEAH.
WH-WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WELL, I THINK I SHOULDN'T LOOK
DIRECTLY AT THEM.
COME ON, SERIOUSLY.
ROSS, THEY'RE REALLY,
REALLY, REALLY WHITE.
YEAH, WHAT WAS WRONG WITH
YOUR OLD... HUMAN TEETH?
OH, I-I DID LEAVE THE GEL ON
A LITTLE LONGER THAN IT SAID TO.
HOW MUCH LONGER?
A-A-A DAY.
ROSS, YOU KNOW THAT TONIGHT IS
YOUR DATE WITH HILLARY?
I KNOW.
THAT'S WHY I DID IT.
COME ON,
ARE THEY REALLY THAT BAD?
NO. NO, NO, NO,
YOU'LL-YOU'LL BE FINE.
HILLARY'S BLIND, RIGHT?
SHE WILL BE
AFTER TONIGHT.
YEAH.
OH, HEY, HEY,
RACHE, UH
DO YOU NOTICE
ANYTHING...
YEAH, YOUR TEETH?
YES, I SAW THEM FROM OUTSIDE.
YOU GUYS ARE NEVER
GOING TO BELIEVE THIS
BUT PHOEBE... MADE OUT...
WITH RALPH LAUREN.
WHAT?
OH, MY GOD.
YEAH, I KNOW.
SHE RAN INTO HIM AT MY OFFICE
AND THEY JUST... MADE OUT
AND THE CRAZIEST THING IS
NOW MY BOSS LIKES ME
BECAUSE I TOLD HER ABOUT IT
AND SHE SAID IT WAS
THE BEST GOSSIP
SHE'D HEARD ALL YEAR.
I AM PROUD OF ALL
MY FRIENDS TODAY.
MY GOD, RACHEL,
I CAN'T BELIEVE
PHOEBE MADE OUT
WITH RALPH LAUREN.
OH, I'M SO JEALOUS.
HI, I'M CHANDLER,
YOUR LIVE-IN BOYFRIEND.
CHANDLER, PLEASE,
COME ON.
LOOK AT HIM.
OH, I AM NO WOMAN, BUT
THAT IS ONE TASTY DISH.
HEY.
HERE.
OOH, WHO'S
THE SILVER FOX?
THAT-THAT IS
YOUR MAKE-OUT BUDDY.
DON'T YOU RECOGNIZE HIM?
OH, WAIT.
OOH, PHOEBE, I LOVE YOU.
KISS ME, PLEASE.
THAT'S NOT RALPH LAUREN.
SOUNDS LIKE HIM, THOUGH.
WHAT?
YEAH, NO, RALPH'S...
DOESN'T LOOK ANYTHING LIKE
THAT GUY.
HE'S-HE'S YOUNG
AND HE'S GOT LONG HAIR
AND A BEARD AND A HACKY SACK.
OH, MY GOD, PHOEBE,
THAT'S NOT RALPH LAUREN.
THAT'S KENNY THE COPY GUY.
WHAT?
OH, G... OH...
AND I TOLD MY BOSS
THAT SOMEONE MADE OUT
WITH RALPH LAUREN.
IF SHE FINDS OUT
THAT I LIED TO HER
SHE IS GOING
TO HATE ME EVEN MORE.
PHOEBE!
WHY WOULD THE COPY GUY
SAY THAT HE'S RALPH LAUREN?
TO GET YOU TO MAKE OUT WITH HIM.
OH.
OKAY, MAYBE
THIS WILL MAKE
YOUR TEETH LOOK
LESS WHITE.
NOPE. NOPE.
OKAY, SO, UH, COLORS
THAT DON'T WORK ARE
BLUE, YELLOW,
GREEN, RED
BLACK, WHITE,
ORANGE AND PURPLE.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M GOING TO DO.
THE DATE STARTS
IN, LIKE, AN HOUR.
HEY, ROSS, MAYBE IF
YOUR SKIN WAS LIGHTER
YOUR TEETH WOULDN'T
LOOK SO BRIGHT.
OH, GREAT.
SO, I ALL NEED TO DO IS
GET SOME NEW SKIN.
THANK YOU.
I'M JUST SAYING
IF WE PUT
JUST A LITTLE BIT
OF MAKEUP ON YOU...
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
WE'RE NOT 13 ANYMORE.
ROSS, THIS IS THE
ONLY THING LEFT
THAT HAS A SHOT
AT WORKING.
BUT WON'T SHE NOTICE
I HAVE MAKEUP ON?
PLEASE, HALF THE GUYS
OUT THERE HAVE MAKEUP ON.
WHAT?
ALL RIGHT,
HALF THE PEOPLE.
I MEAN... WILL YOU
JUST TRY IT AND SEE?
NO, I AM NOT
PUTTING ON MAKE-UP.
( knocking at door )
HELLO?
OH, GOOD.
ROSS, COULD YOU PUT UP SOME
OF THESE FLYERS FOR ME?
NO! DEMON! DEMON!
NOW OUR DRAWERS
WILL SMELL NICE
AND WE DIDN'T WASTE
THESE PANTYHOSE.
YES, GOD FORBID WE
THROW OUT OLD UNDERWEAR.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M-I'M GOING TO... I'M
GOING TO GO OVER TO JOEY'S.
WE'RE SUPPOSE TO ORGANIZE
THE WRAPPING-PAPER DRAWER.
YES, BUT I FEEL LIKE I'VE
REALLY GOTTEN IN TOUCH
WITH MY FEMININE SIDE
ENOUGH TODAY, YOU KNOW.
IN FACT, I THINK
WE'RE TWO SACHETS
AWAY FROM BECOMING
A LESBIAN COUPLE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THIS HAS BEEN
KIND OF A GIRLIE DAY.
YOU'RE RIGHT. I'M SORRY.
NAH, NAH,
THAT'S OKAY.
I-I FEEL LIKE I NEED
TO BE IN A GUY PLACE...
YOU KNOW, DO KIND OF,
LIKE, A MAN THING.
YEAH. GO OVER TO JOEY'S.
GO OVER TO JOEY'S
AND-AND DRINK SOME BEER
AND HAMMER UP
SOME DRYWALL.
YOU KNOW, WHEN
GUYS HANG OUT
THEY DON'T JUST DRINK BEER
AND HAMMER UP DRYWALL.
WHEN GIRLS HANG OUT,
WE DON'T HAVE PILLOW FIGHTS
IN OUR UNDERWEAR.
I'M SORRY.
WE DO.
I DON'T KNOW
WHY I SAID THAT.
HEY, CHANDLER.
COME ON IN.
WE'RE KNITTING
POT HOLDERS.
NO THANKS, JOSEPHINE.
( door shuts )
HEY, ROSS, I WAS
WONDERING IF...
OH, MY GOD!
WHERE ARE ALL THE MEN?
( door closes )
OH, HI, KIM.
HI, RACHEL.
REMEMBER THAT THING
I TOLD YOU
THAT HAPPENED YESTERDAY?
WELL, IT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
YOU DIDN'T CANCEL THE
FABRIC ORDER FROM TAIWAN?
OKAY, TWO THINGS
DIDN'T HAPPEN.
BUT, NO, REMEMBER I TOLD YOU
THAT SOMEONE MADE OUT WITH
RALPH LAUREN
IN THE COPY ROOM?
WELL, IT TURNS OUT
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
THAT'S NOT TRUE?
NO.
OH, THAT'S
INTERESTING
BECAUSE I CHECKED.
AND ONLY ONE
KEY CARD WAS USED
TO ACCESS THE COPY MACHINE
YESTERDAY DURING LUNCH
AND THAT KEY CARD
BELONGED TO YOU, RACHEL.
OH, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
OH, GOD, YOU THINK
I MADE OUT WITH HIM?
LISTEN TO ME.
IF YOU THINK
SLEEPING WITH RALPH
IS GOING TO GET YOU MY JOB,
YOU ARE SADLY MISTAKEN.
I DON'T WANT YOUR JOB.
I DON'T!
THIS IS SUCH A MISTAKE.
I DID NOT
MAKE OUT WITH HIM.
NOBODY MADE OUT WITH HIM.
I DID NOT USE
MY KEY CARD YESTERDAY.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
HOW TO USE MY KEY CARD.
HI, RALPH.
HI, KIM.
YEAH, NOTHING HAPPENED.
YOU COULD CUT THE
SEXUAL TENSION IN
HERE WITH A KNIFE.
AND AFTER THAT, WHAT COULD
I DO EXCEPT BECOME A CHEF.
MM-HMM.
AND SOMEDAY SOON, I HOPE
TO OPEN MY OWN RESTAURANT.
MMM.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE A
REALLY GREAT LISTENER.
MOST GUYS I GO OUT WITH,
THEY JUST TALK AND TALK.
MM-HMM.
AFTER A WHILE, IT'S
JUST, LIKE, SHUT YOUR
MOUTH, YOU KNOW?
( stifled chuckle):
HMM-HMM!
I'VE PROBABLY BEEN
TALKING TOO MUCH.
WHY DON'T WE TALK
ABOUT YOU A LITTLE BIT?
MM-MMM.
COME ON, I
WANT TO KNOW.
HMM-HMM-HMM.
OKAY.
I, UM, I'M FROM
LONG ISLAND.
I CAME TO THE CITY
FOR COLLEGE.
UM, I, UH,
I HAVE A FIVE-YEAR-OLD SON.
AND IN MY SPARE TIME
I LIKE TO READ SPY NOVELS
BUT LET'S TALK MORE
ABOUT YOU, HMM?
SO WHAT'S REALLY NEAT IS
IF YOU SEAR THE STEMS
OF THE FLOWERS FIRST
IN A FRYING PAN,
YOU'RE ARRANGEMENT
WILL LOOK FRESH MUCH LONGER.
OH, MY GOD, JOEY, THAT
IS SUCH A GREAT TIP.
MONICA, CAN YOU EXCUSE US
FOR A SECOND?
I NEED TO TALK TO THE GIRL
WITH THE FLOWERS.
OKAY.
OH, JOEY, COME OVER LATER
'CAUSE I'M GOING TO TEACH YOU
HOW TO MAKE A BIRD FEEDER
OUT OF JUST A PINECONE
AND SOME PEANUT BUTTER.
OH... I LOVE BIRDS.
WHAT IS THE MATTER WITH YOU?
WHAT?
YOU'RE ARRANGING FLOWERS!
YOU GOT DEAD FLOWERS!
YOU GOT TO A PICTURE
OF A BABY DRESSED LIKE FLOWERS!
THIS IS NOT JOEY.
HEY, HEY, LOOK, I AM
STILL JOEY, OKAY?
FLOWERS, THEY'RE JUST
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE
NICE TO LOOK AT.
AND THAT HAPPENS TO BE A
PICTURE BY A FAMOUS ARTIST
OF A FAMOUS BABY.
YOU'RE TURNING INTO A WOMAN.
NO, I'M NOT.
WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT?
THAT'S JUST MEAN.
NOW I'VE UPSET YOU?
WHAT DID I SAY?
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU SAID
IT'S JUST THE
WAY YOU SAID IT.
OH, MY GOD!
I'M A WOMAN!
SO NOW SHE THINKS
THAT I MADE OUT WITH HIM
AND THAT I DID IT TO GET
HER JOB.
WELL, WHY DIDN'T YOU
JUST TELL HER THE TRUTH?
I DID.
BUT SHE DOESN'T THINK THAT
ANYONE WOULD BE STUPID ENOUGH
TO CONFUSE KENNY THE COPY GUY
WITH RALPH LAUREN.
WELL, HEY, WHAT IF KENNY
WERE THE REAL BRAINS
BEHIND THE WHOLE
COMPANY, YOU KNOW?
WHAT IF KENNY HIRED
THAT RALPH LAUREN GUY
TO BE THE PRETTY
FRONT MAN, HUH?
DID SHE EVER THINK OF THAT?
YOU WERE WITH KENNY TODAY,
WEREN'T YOU?
JUST FOR A SECOND.
OH... PHOEBE, WHAT AM
I GOING TO DO?
WELL, THE ONLY
THING YOU CAN DO.
SLEEP WITH RALPH LAUREN.
I'M NOT GOING TO SLEEP
WITH RALPH LAUREN.
I MEAN, I COULD,
BUT I WOULDN'T.
OH, SLEEP WITH KENNY.
THAT WOULDN'T HELP ME.
OH, YES, IT WOULD.
I'VE HAD A REALLY
GOOD TIME TONIGHT.
MMM.
YOU KNOW, I RARELY
CONNECT WITH SOMEONE
THIS MUCH ON
THE FIRST DATE.
HMM-MM, HMM-MM.
ME, NEITHER.
I'VE HAD A REALLY GOOD
TIME, TOO, YOU KNOW.
ARE YOU GOING TO
EAT THAT BREAD?
OH, I-I-I
JUST LIKE THE SMELL.
( sniffs )...MMM.
YOU MAKE ME LAUGH.
HM-MMM.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO MOVE
OVER TO THE COUCH?
MM-HMM.
MAYBE I'LL JUST TURN
DOWN THE LIGHTS A LITTLE.
HOW ABOUT ALL THE WAY?
OKAY.
WOW, COOL POSTER.
OR, SHOULD I SAY GROOVY POSTER?
SO, UH, WHERE WERE WE?
ARE THOSE YOUR TEETH?
OH, YOU CAN SEE THEM, HUH?
YES.
THEY'RE INSANELY WHITE.
YEAH, I DID THAT FOR YOU.
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU?
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH ME?
YOU'VE GOT A BLACK LIGHT!
IT'S 1999!
OH, GOOD.
KIM, HI.
HI, RACHEL.
OH, I'VE BEEN
MEANING TO ASK YOU.
HAVE YOU SEEN THE NEW
RALPH LAUREN SHEETS?
WHAT AM I THINKING?
OF COURSE YOU HAVE.
OKAY-- OKAY, LOOK.
I'M SORRY
THAT I LIED TO YOU BEFORE.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
RALPH AND I WERE AN ITEM,
BUT WE'RE NOT ANYMORE.
OH, REALLY?
YEAH.
HE DUMPED ME.
HE SAID,
"RACHEL, I CAN'T DO THIS.
"EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE A VERY,
"VERY, VERY BEAUTIFUL WOMAN
"I CAN'T DO THIS.
I'M MARRIED AND I'M SORRY."
AND THEN--
I DON'T KNOW WHY--
BUT HE SAID, "AND YOU
WILL NEVER GET PROMOTED
"ESPECIALLY NOT ABOVE KIM,
WHO IS AN INTEGRAL COG
IN THE RALPH LAUREN MACHINE."
YOU EXPECT ME
TO BELIEVE THAT...
HI, RALPH.
HI, KIM.
OH, MY GOD.
HE JUST GAVE YOU THE COLDEST
LOOK I HAVE EVER SEEN.
IT'S LIKE HE HATES YOU.
THEN IT IS TRUE?
OF COURSE IT'S TRUE.
AND IT HURTS SO BAD.
OH, HONEY, COME HERE.
OH, IT'LL BE OKAY.
IT'S JUST WE'VE
ALL BEEN THERE.
Y-Y-Y-YOU AND RALPH?
KENNY THE COPY BOY.
HEY!
HEY, UH...
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
ARE YOU UPSET?
I'M SORRY, BUT WE GOT TO GET RID
OF ALL THIS GIRLIE STUFF
IN HERE.
I, UH, I GOT TO BE A MAN.
OKAY?
THE LIVING ROOM HAS TO REMAIN
A GUY PLACE, OKAY?
THAT'S JUST THE WAY
IT HAS TO BE.
WELL, IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT,
I'LL JUST PUT IT ALL IN MY ROOM.
GOOD.
GREAT... GREAT.
AND, UH, THANKS
FOR BEING SO UNDERSTANDING.
I MEAN, I DIDN'T WANT
TO MAKE A BIG DEAL
OUT OF THIS, YOU KNOW.
WELL, BUT YOU COULD, UH,
PUT THE PICTURE
OF THE FAMOUS BABY
IN MY ROOM.
I MEAN, IF YOU WANT TO.
OKAY.
AND, UH, MAYBE
THE WATERING CAN THERE.
SURE.
AND A COUPLE OF THESE
LITTLE TINY BOXES.
JOEY, DO YOU WANT ME TO
PUT IT ALL IN YOUR ROOM?
OKAY.